#### Contact

6232626866 (Mobile) cw653@cornell.edu

www.linkedin.com/in/cndwng (LinkedIn) cndwng.com (Portfolio)

### Top Skills

UX design Python

Java

Languages

Mandarin

English

Honors-Awards
BigRed//Hacks 2016 Best UI/UX

# **Cindy Wang**

Product Designer Brooklyn

## Summary

I'm a product designer currently working in fintech, specializing in building design systems. I graduated with a Computer Science degree from Cornell University in 2019, and previously worked in the e-commerce space. Passionate about mental and physical health. Open to new projects and opportunities!

## Experience

FactSet

1 year 9 months

Senior UX Specialist April 2022 - Present (1 month) New York, New York, United States

- Design, prototype, test, and build dozens of responsive & accessible design system components and patterns
- Manage and organize library assets and onboarding materials for new hires
- Oversee app design teams to maintain consistency in applications
- Led company-wide design initiative to elevate old applications to modern visuals

**UX Specialist** 

August 2020 - April 2022 (1 year 9 months)

New York, New York, United States

Spoak

**Product Designer** 

August 2021 - Present (9 months)

Next Jump

**UX** Designer

August 2019 - June 2020 (11 months)

Greater New York City Area

- Create mockups and develop front end components for e-commerce employee

rewards platform (Perks at Work) that drives over \$2B in sales annually

- Built a fundraising platform with a team that raised over \$170k for NYC hospitals

and frontline workers

- Plan site themes and CRM emails for customer base of over 79 million employees, including a Valentine's Day event that increased gross profit per flowers order by 20%
- Manage video production, social media, and print/graphic materials for a free online course program bringing over 24k unique participants per week

Cornell University
Teaching Assistant
January 2019 - May 2019 (5 months)
Ithaca, New York Area

- Course staff for INFO 4320: Introduction to Rapid Prototyping & Physical Computing
- Taught students skills with microcontrollers, 3D printing, and laser cutting
- Provided mentorship for group projects, held office hours, and graded assignments

#### FactSet

UX Design Intern June 2018 - August 2018 (3 months) Norwalk, CT

- Built a responsive UI component library of hundreds of components in Figma as part of an effort to implement an atomic design system
- Collaborated with interaction designers to produce mockups for product development

#### StartupTree

**Product Designer** 

June 2017 - January 2018 (8 months)

Ithaca, New York Area

- Completely revamped web platform and the brand's web style guide to have a more consistent

interface and be more user-friendly

- Designed and oversaw implementation of a module for applications and competitions with

in-platform judging capabilities, leading to dozens of schools signing with StartupTree

- Created mockups for the platform's mobile application

Cornell University Survey Research Institute Research Assistant November 2016 - May 2017 (7 months) Ithaca, NY

- Conducted interviews for academic research on behalf of Cornell faculty

## Education

**Cornell University** 

Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Computer Science · (2015 - 2019)